IICE has launched a new plan
called Elevate. This plan has
five such things that are not available in any of the
health insurance companies till date.
What is there in this plan that
other companies are not offering, so we will
find out. Watch the video till the end. If you are
new to the channel, then subscribe to the channel
and do not forget to press the bell icon
so that in the future you can get all the insurance and
finance related information
that customers are looking for today. So
we will start the video directly here. So
guys, I was talking
about IICE Lamba's Elevate plan. So,
first of all, in this plan you get an infighting
claim amount, an infighting bonus, and an
infighting.
These are five such things which have
completely changed this plan and have
completely changed the entire health insurance industry. So, do
not forget to watch the video till the end. First, let us talk about the
basic benefits which are in the policy
and before the benefits, let us talk about
what is eligible and what is not.  What are these shares, what are the
conditions, what are the waiting periods, what are the
advances, what are the five best advances that
I have told you which you are going to get in
this policy, the
entry age in this policy is 18 and the maximum entry
age is 125 years, secondly let's
talk about sum in short, how much is your coverage in this,
you have coverage of 5 lakhs, 75 lakhs, 10 lakhs,
15 lakhs, 20 lakhs, 25 lakhs, 50 lakhs, 1 crore,
3 crores and there is also unlimited coverage,
you can take this policy for one year, two years, three years,
you get additional discount on taking it for two years and three years, you must definitely
take that, plus if you want a policy, then you can have
husband, wife and three others together in a family floater policy, so
you
can take a policy for a maximum of five members, a
child will be considered in one policy
till the age of 30, age of one child is covered
in the same policy, now let's talk about basic benefits,
day care surgery is all
covered in the policy, there is a list  It
means that there are some surgeries in which
you do
not need to be admitted in the hospital, you go for five to seven hours for the whole day
and get treatment done and
come back, then that surgery is also covered under the policy,
plus under the policy, your pre
and post hospitalization, that is,
expenses for 90 days before admission and
expenses for 180 days after discharge, you can also
get the money back, and if we talk about organ donor, then
under the policy, your
organ donor is covered up to the sum in shot, that
means if you are donating your organ to
someone like kidney etc.,
you are donating any body part to someone, then
its amount will be covered up to the sum in shot,
up to the sum in shot means whatever
coverage you have given, 10 lakh, 20 lakh, 30 lakh, 50
lakh, whatever the next benefit, home
treatment, that is, if you
want treatment at home, then you can get the treatment done at home as well, it
is necessary to have treatment for three days, then you can cover that expense also.  If you want to get
treatment at home,
either the hospital bed is not available or the
doctor has advised that your condition is
critical, then you can get treatment at home. There is
another option, it is called
if there is a curfew or such a condition outside, then
in that condition also you can get treatment at home. If we
talk about road ambulance, then that
too is covered up to summary shots in the policy.
Ayurvedic, Unani, Siddha,
Homeopathic treatment etc., all of that is also
covered up to summary shots in the policy. You also have a reset benefit in this policy.
It is called reset benefit,
like for example, you took a policy of 10 lakhs,
10 lakhs got exhausted, a claim came again, you will
get 10 lakhs again. If a
claim comes again, then you will get 10 lakhs again. What I
mean to say is that whatever coverage you are taking,
you can take that coverage as many times as you want
and the extra coverage you
get, you can use it for any disease.
There is no condition. Let us
talk about bonus which is called no.  It is called claim bonus.
You also have a no claim bonus inside the policy. You will
get bonus five times
at 20, 20, 20, 20. By doing 20, 20, your policy of Rs. 10 will
increase the coverage from Rs. 20. I have
taken the example of Rs. 10 lakh, so I am telling you in terms of Rs. 10 lakh, that
means your policy of Rs.
10 lakh will become of Rs. 12 lakh, then Rs. 14 lakh, then Rs. 16 lakh,
then Rs. 18 lakh, then Rs. 20 lakh. If you do
not make a claim continuously for five years, then
this is your next benefit, your wellness
benefit. What you get in this is that you get a
discount of up to Rs. 30 on renewal. Next year, if
you want, you can reduce your premium.
Next year, you have to download an app of
ICICI Bank. By
downloading that app, what you do with it is that you
can collect some points.
How to collect those points? To collect those points,
you have to follow the steps per day. When you
follow those steps, you will get
points on that.  You will keep getting them, if you
want, you can avail a discount of up to 30% at the time of renal.
Another important
thing is bariatric surgery.
What does bariatric surgery mean?
Obesity surgery is
not covered by many insurance companies,
but under this plan, that too
is covered up to some extent in short. If we talk about
modern treatment,
what does modern treatment mean? Earlier, it was
not covered under insurance;
if it was, then it was covered under very limited companies
or it was available up to Rs 1 lakh.
Modern treatment is that
where you are going to make a claim
and the treatment in which you are being
treated robotically, like
chemotherapy etc., okay,
what is it in that condition that today's technology has become
so advanced that there were
very few companies in India which covered such operations according to
robotics, technology-
wise modern treatment, which is called,
okay, so that type of treatment
is also covered under the policy today, the most
important thing up to some extent in short  It
is covered which no other company is providing
except one or two. You
can also take maternity coverage in this plan, that
is also covered under your policy. Now let's talk about
waiting periods. Dental
is covered in the policy from the same day you
took the policy. If you have to claim for normal and critical illness, then
you
can claim after 30 days. If you have to claim for surgery,
then all surgeries
are covered only after 30 days, but there are some surgeries
which are covered after 2 years
like cataract, stone, hernia, slipped sinus,
uterus, fibroid, ENT. In this way,
in every company, there are 14 to 15 or maximum
171 surgeries which are
covered after 2 years under the insurance.
If you already have any problem, then
you will get a claim for that. After 3 years,
your premium will be calculated under this policy,
according to the zone. The
company has kept four types of zones
in the policy. Zone A  Zone B, Zone C, Zone D means that
if we talk about cities in Zone A, it's
Mumbai, Ghaziabad, I'm
talking about big cities, Delhi, etc.
Okay, big cities like that, they're Zone A, Zone B,
like Pune,
Kolkata, Bangalore, in this
way, if we talk about Zone C, like
Chhattisgarh, Himachal Pradesh,
Jammu and Kashmir, in this way, the cities of your Zone 3 will
come under Zone D. Now let's talk about
Zone D. All the remaining
cities, even the smallest ones, will all
come under Zone D. But the most
important thing is that under this policy,
you won't have to pay zone-wise copayment. This
means that if you are in Zone D, that is,
you live in the smallest city, and you are
going for treatment in Zone A, that is,
you are going for treatment in a big city, then
you can get the treatment done. It's
not like you will get a claim on 80% or 90%.
You will get a full 100% claim. Now let's
talk about how you can
save money on renewal.  You can, as I
told you, the wellness option is your
benefit, in which you
get a discount of up to 30%. You have to follow some steps on renewal, based on that, the
second is yours, if you
renew the policy 30 days before the next year's fair, then you will be
given an additional discount of 2.5%. The
third option is yours, if you
want the policy, you can take it for 2 years or 3 years, you
get a discount of 10% on 2 years,
you get a discount of up to 15% on 3 years.
You can add many advances or riders in this policy,
what are the riders, first of all
comes yours for critical illness, under this policy
your 20 critical illnesses are covered, the maximum
coverage is available up to 50 lakhs
and you can
take this cover only for customers up to the age of 50 years,
plus a personal
accident add-on is also available in this policy.  The
add-on is available for coverage up to Rs 50 lakh
and customers up to 65 years of age can avail it. The
next add-on is your voluntary co-payment.
What this means is that if you wish, you
can reduce your premium. If you have taken a policy of Rs
10 lakh and feel that the premium is
high, then take a co-payment of Rs 10 lakh. What this
means is that whatever claim comes, the
company will pay you Rs 90 lakh, but you have to
pay from your pocket. The options you will
get in this are Rs 10 lakh, Rs 20 lakh, Rs 30 lakh, Rs 40 lakh, Rs 50 lakh.
Your maternity coverage is available under this policy,
but I
forgot to tell you about the waiting period for maternity. Let me
tell you that the
waiting period for maternity is two years.
If you wish, you can reduce it to one
year. The name of the rider is
Option to Reduce Maternity Waiting Period.
Your consultation is also available under this policy. If you
wish, you can
download the app and get it through video audio.  You
can do tele consultation through video audio, if
you have any problem then you
can discuss it with the company doctor, that
option is also available in the policy and you
can do this unlimited times, there are many more
addons which you can include in the policy,
but the addon which I am going to talk about now are
five such addons which are the
best due to which this plan has become so
famous, so the first addon is
your inflated bonus, for example, you took a policy of 10 lakhs, if a claim comes then you will get 1 crore, but this will be available only once in the entire life, the third addon is your inflating bonus, in this policy if
you want then you
can give as much bonus as you want, there is no limit, the
coverage will keep increasing, but this Kamal Vi
bonus is known as power booster.  If it comes then
you can include it in your policy.
After this is your
infighting.
What it means is that there are
five such diseases in the policy which you
can claim after 90 days in the policy. It
comes in the name of jump start rider.
BP, diabetes, asthma, cholesterol. There is another
disease, if you want to know its name,
comment in the comment box. Illness. After this, in the last season,
your infighting will
again get 10 lakhs. It is over, then you will get 10
lakhs. You can take as much as you want, but
you can take 10 lakhs from the company. So,
these were five such advances which are the
best and the most different in the line of health insurance.
If you are going to take health insurance for your
family or for yourself, then
definitely think about this plan. It is a very good plan. The
premium is also not so high that
you feel that adding all these things will
increase the premium a lot. It is not like that.
Many people will find this premium affordable. So
this was the
Elevate plan of IIC under health insurance. If you have any
doubt about this plan,  If you
want to know about any condition, any waiting period, any benefits, any add-ons, then you can call us.
Your number is available in the description. And
if you want to purchase any health insurance policy or
any life insurance policy or any
kind of insurance, then
you can call us.
Your number is available in the description.
So now we will end the video here. Those
who have not subscribed to my channel, please
subscribe to the channel. We will meet like this
in the next video. Then take
care, bye bye, good bye and bye bye
[Music]